wadtube.com 2014-04-27

# Privacy Policy | Wad Tube

**Privacy Policy for wadtube.com**

This document describes how we treat personal information related to your use of wadtube.com (the "Website"), including information you provide when using it.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at webmaster@wadtube.com.

At Website, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Website and how it is used.

We expressly and strictly limit use of the Website to adults over 18 years of age or the age of majority in the individual`s jurisdiction, whichever is greater. Anyone under this age is strictly forbidden from using the Website. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained this age.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, Website makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), country of origin and other non- personal information about your computer or device such as web requests, browser type, browser language, referring URL, operating system and date and time of requests to analyze trends, administer the site, track user`s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

When you use the Website, we may send cookies to your computer to uniquely identify your browser session. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies.  
We use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....  
JuicyAds

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Website send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
Website has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Website`s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

**Disclosures of Information**

We may be required to release certain data to comply with legal obligations or in order to enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements. We may also release certain data to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users and others. This includes providing information to other companies or organizations like the police or governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against or prosecution of any illegal activity, whether or not it is identified in the Terms of Use.
